<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE MudletPackage>
<MudletPackage version="1.001">
    <TriggerPackage>
        <Trigger isActive="yes" isFolder="no" isTempTrigger="no" isMultiline="no" isPerlSlashGOption="no" isColorizerTrigger="no" isFilterTrigger="no" isSoundTrigger="no" isColorTrigger="no" isColorTriggerFg="no" isColorTriggerBg="no">
            <name>City</name>
            <script>--example trigger only, this will probably never fire for you
demonnic.chat:append(&quot;City&quot;)</script>
            <triggerType>0</triggerType>
            <conditonLineDelta>39</conditonLineDelta>
            <mStayOpen>0</mStayOpen>
            <mCommand></mCommand>
            <packageName></packageName>
            <mFgColor>#ff0000</mFgColor>
            <mBgColor>#ffff00</mBgColor>
            <mSoundFile></mSoundFile>
            <colorTriggerFgColor>#000000</colorTriggerFgColor>
            <colorTriggerBgColor>#000000</colorTriggerBgColor>
            <regexCodeList>
                <string>(NewYork):</string>
            </regexCodeList>
            <regexCodePropertyList>
                <integer>2</integer>
            </regexCodePropertyList>
        </Trigger>
    </TriggerPackage>
    <TimerPackage/>
    <AliasPackage/>
    <ActionPackage/>
    <ScriptPackage>
        <ScriptGroup isActive="yes" isFolder="yes">
            <name>YATCOCONFIG</name>
            <packageName></packageName>
            <script>demonnic = demonnic or {}
demonnic.chat = demonnic.chat or {}
demonnic.chat.config = demonnic.chat.config or {}</script>
            <eventHandlerList/>
            <Script isActive="yes" isFolder="no">
                <name>Configuration Options</name>
                <packageName></packageName>
                <script>--[[
This is where all of the configuration options can be set. 
Anything I've put in this script object can be changed, but please do pay attention to what you're doing.
If you change one of the values to something it shouldn't be, you could break it. 
]]

--This is where you tell it to use tabbed chat.
demonnic.chat.use = true

--[[
This is where you put what container to put the tabbed chat stuff into. Make it
equal to the actual container object you want it in, or false for none. Defaults to false
Which is to say if you want to put the tabbed chat stuff into a container made using 
uiRight = Geyser.Container:new()

you would put

demonnic.chat.useContainer = uiRight

and if you don't want it in a container you would put

demonnic.chat.useContainer = false
]]

demonnic.chat.useContainer = false

--[[
The timestamp option is set here.
Set to false if you do not want any timestamps displayed for chat.
If you do want it displayed, set to the string for the format you wish. 
see http://wiki.mudlet.org/w/Manual:Lua_Functions#getTime for information
how to format the string
]]
demonnic.chat.config.timestamp = &quot;HH:mm:ss&quot;

--[[ Should we use our own colors for the timestamp?
Set to true if you want to specify foreground and background colors
for the timestamp.
Set to false if you want the timestamps background and foreground
colors to match that of the mud output.
]]
demonnic.chat.config.timestampCustomColor = false
--[[
and what foreground color? You can either use one of the 'named' colors
(see http://wiki.mudlet.org/images/c/c3/ShowColors.png for available colors)
demonnic.chat.config.timestampFG = &quot;slate_grey&quot;

Or you can use a table of R,G,B values. 
demonnic.chat.config.timestampFG = {
  255,
    0,
    0,
}
then the foreground for the timestamp would be 255 read, 100 green, and 0 blue
]]
demonnic.chat.config.timestampFG = &quot;red&quot;

--and background? Same rules as for the foreground above
demonnic.chat.config.timestampBG = &quot;blue&quot;

--[[
This is where you say what corner of the screen you want the tabbed chat on
Valid settings are &quot;topright&quot;, &quot;topleft&quot;, &quot;bottomright&quot;, &quot;bottomleft&quot;
]]--
demonnic.chat.config.location = &quot;topright&quot;

--[[
This is a table of channels you would like.
AKA the place you tell the script what tabs you want.
Each entry must be a string. The defaults should be a pretty effective guide.
]]

demonnic.chat.config.channels = {
  &quot;All&quot;,
  &quot;City&quot;,
  &quot;Guild&quot;,
  &quot;Clans&quot;,
  &quot;Local&quot;,
}


--Set this to the name of the channel you want to have everything sent to. 
--Per the default, this would be the &quot;All&quot; channel. If you have a different name for it:
--
--demonnic.chat.config.Alltab = &quot;Bucket&quot;  
--
--And if you don't want it turned on at all:
--
--demonnic.chat.config.Alltab = false

demonnic.chat.config.Alltab = &quot;All&quot;

--Set this to the name of the channel you want to display your map. Set to &quot;&quot; if you
--don't want to display the map in your YATCO tabs
demonnic.chat.config.Maptab = &quot;&quot;


---------------------------------------------------------------------------------
--                                                                             --
--The infamous blinking stuff!!!                                               --
--                                                                             --
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------

--[[
Do you want tabs to blink when you get new messages, until you click on the tab?
True if yes, false if no.
]]
demonnic.chat.config.blink = true

--How long (in seconds) between blinks? For example, 1 would mean a 1 second pause in between blinks.
demonnic.chat.config.blinkTime = 3

--Blink if the bucket tab (&quot;All&quot; by default, but configured above) is in focus?
demonnic.chat.config.blinkFromAll = false




--Font size for the chat messages

demonnic.chat.config.fontSize = 9

--[[
Should we preserve the formatting of the text. 
Or should we set the background of it to match the window color?
Set this to false if you want the background for all chat to match the background of the window.
Useful if you change the background from black, and don't like the way the pasted chat makes blocks in it
]]

demonnic.chat.config.preserveBackground = false

--[[
Gag the chat lines in the main window?
defaults to false, set to true if you want to gag.
]]

demonnic.chat.config.gag = false

--[[
Number of lines of chat visible at once. 
Will determine how tall the window for the chats is.
]]

demonnic.chat.config.lines = 45

--[[
Number of characters to wrap the chatlines at.
This will also determine how wide the chat windows are.
]]

demonnic.chat.config.width = 60

--[[
Set the color for the active tab. R,G,B format.
The default here is a brightish green
]]

demonnic.chat.config.activeColors = {
  r = 0,
  g = 180,
  b = 0,
}

--[[
Set the color for the inactive tab. R,G,B format.
The default here is a drab grey
]]

demonnic.chat.config.inactiveColors = {
  r = 60,
  g = 60,
  b = 60,
}

--[[
Set the color for the chat window itself. R,G,B format.
Defaulted to the black of my twisted hardened soul. Or something.
]]

demonnic.chat.config.windowColors = {
  r = 0,
  g = 0,
  b = 0,
}

--[[
Set the color for the text on the active tab. Uses color names.
Set the default to purple. So the tab you're looking at, by default will be purple on bright green. 
Did I mention I'm a bit colorblind?
]]

demonnic.chat.config.activeTabText = &quot;purple&quot;

--[[
Set the color for the text on the inactive tabs. Uses color names.
Defaulted this to white. So the tabs you're not looking at will be white text on boring grey background.
]]

demonnic.chat.config.inactiveTabText = &quot;white&quot;

--[[
have to make sure a currentTab is set... 
so we'll use the one for the bucket, or the first one in the channels table
Or, you know... what it's currently set to, if it's already set.
]]
demonnic.chat.currentTab = demonnic.chat.currentTab or demonnic.chat.config.Alltab or demonnic.chat.config.channels[1]
</script>
                <eventHandlerList/>
            </Script>
        </ScriptGroup>
    </ScriptPackage>
    <KeyPackage/>
</MudletPackage>
